ALL PERSONS, LOCATIONS, RELIGIONS,
INCIDENTS, AND ORGANIZATIONS IN THIS DRAMA
ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS HAVE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER PARENTAL SUPERVISION
SCENES INVOLVING ANIMALS WERE FILMED
SAFELY WITH EXPERT ADVICE AND COOPERATION
Put the Moon Donuts
-behind the Chili Crunch.
-Hold on.
Swap their places.
No, Chili Crunch should be in front.
Are you disrespecting Moon Donuts?
Chili Crunch generates far more revenue.
It's too far back.
-Move it forward.
-Okay.
Look…
Yes, that's perfect.
That's way too far in front.
Finally, the Hot Chocolate Chips.
Where should this go?
It used to be our company's
best-selling product.
Should we put it right in the center?
If Spicy SweeTato Chips were released,
they could've been here together.
Wait, could you come
hold this for a second?
Come on.
Should I hold the bottom?
No, it's fine. Move that…
BROTHER CLEANING
-Is Namgung ignoring your calls, too?
-Forget it.
It's for the best, for Namgung's sake.
Who could even handle Mi-do?
Look who's talking.
Jeez, you scared me!
You were whining about being broke
when you wanted to get married.
So I helped you get married,
then you got divorced.
Wow, how pathetic.
Why are you bringing that up?
It's not like you bought me a house.
It was only like five million won.
"Only five million won"?
Hey!
Someone with 100 million
lending five million
and someone with ten million
lending five million…
No, wait.
Someone with 5.12 million won
lending five million is not the same.
The value is completely different!
I gave you my entire life savings
at the time, okay?
That five million
wasn't just five million.
It was worth
more than 500 million won.
So you have no right
to use the word "only"!
Got it?
Did I not pay you back? I paid you back.
Did you even hear a word I just said?
That five million was worth
over 500 million,
so you should've paid back
500 million, you idiot!
What a crook.
A crook? You're an idiot,
so you're a crook--
-Then I--
-Stop it, both of you!
I'm going to throw up.
To my deeply beloved Namgung-Tush.
Must be nice.
The girl you had a crush on forever
finally became yours.
Treat me right.
You still have a long way to go.
Try harder.
What the hell?
YEONG-DO
-What's up?
-We're in big trouble. What do we do?
Mi-do's missing.
What?
I'm losing my mind.
Where the hell did she go?
You need to get over here. I'm at…
Why would I go there?
I told you I broke up with her.
Check the playground.
Look in the tube slide.
You're going to make up anyway.
Aren't you worried about Lee Mi-do?
-If something happens--
-What does that have to do with me?
She and I are strangers now.
I'm just going to do whatever I want.
I'll join a matchmaking agency
and go on blind dates.
And also,
I'll go on  I Am Solo Too,
Single's Paradise,  all of them!
TO MY DEEPLY BELOVED NAMGUNG-TUSH
Do you have volume eight of  Slam Dunk?
2. CAN WE EVER BE STRANGERS?
NON-DISCLOSURE
AND RELATIONSHIP TERMINATION AGREEMENT
This agreement states
you won't reveal
your relationship with the CEO.
SIGNATURE
Oh, right.
I'll be taking care of the matter
regarding Director Lee.
You heard, right?
This is Attorney Han Tae-seung.
I heard through Producer Oh Yeon-ju
that you declined.
Let's meet one more time
and try to work things out.
I look forward to your response.
If we go to trial, you'll lose
money, time, and emotional energy,
not to mention your reputation.
Why would you choose the hard way?
I'll wait for your call.
Ms. Lee, I handled your mediation request
that you submitted
to the Film Industry Grievance Portal.
It'd hurt both sides if this went public.
I'll wait for your call.
This bastard!
25TH
I HAVE SOMETHING IMPORTANT THIS MONTH
CAN YOU SEND IT A WEEK EARLY?
MY DEAR DICTATOR VER. 3
I waited, but I never heard from you.
I've done my research,
so I know where you usually show up.
Ahyeon Library,
Hanpung Bookstore, Haneul Park,
Jake Coffee Gongdeok Branch, Nemo's Cafe…
Oh.
Yeoju Auntie's Home-Style Fish Grill.
Wow.
Their charcoal-grilled mackerel is crazy.
You really should sign the settlement.
We'll guarantee
up to 30% of the copyright.
SETTLEMENT AGREEMENT
Are you married?
That's random.
So it wasn't this bastard.
"This bastard"?
Show up like this again, and you're dead.
Your mom owns a building in Yeonhui-dong.
Is that why you're so fearless?
We have to know our opponent well.
We call this
a preliminary fact-checking review.
Your older brother runs
a pipe cleaning company.
Your younger brother's
the first Korean diver
to set a record
in the constant weight category.
And your long-time boyfriend…
I know you broke up recently.
Was it because of this?
Wow, what a piece of trash.
What a bastard.
You don't abandon someone
during tough times.
Right?
We have to know our opponent well.
We call this
a preliminary fact-checking review.
Your older brother runs
a pipe cleaning company…
Unauthorized and unjust background checks.
Illegal interference in mediation.
Threats using my family.
Inciting fear under the guise of a deal.
This will be very helpful in court.
Thank you.
Let's add one more.
Property damage.
Oh, I'll buy a new phone
and send it to you today.
Ms. Lee.
I'm drowning in work lately.
So I wanted to settle
this trivial case and be done,
which is why I was being nice.
But you're making this difficult.
Since you want it so badly,
I'll see you in court.
You better be fully prepared.
Bill me for it.
Oh, and make sure to send me
the newest phone model.
In white, with 1 terabyte of storage.
I know the reason why
the fourth sample had issues.
Want me to tell you?
See you at Omyeong's Pyongyang
Cold Noodles on the 9th at noon.
I'll tell you then.
Um…
Ouch! Jeez.
What's this?
What are you doing here?
Jeez, you're always so impatient.
Are you here
because of the sample schedule?
Unbelievable, man.
-Jeez.
-We need to talk.
Come on.
You forgot about our appointment.
Oh.
I'm sorry, but I never said I'd go.
Why not?
You wanted to know
why there was a difference in taste
between the lab and factory samples.
I heard you even checked
the sweet potato farms on-site, no?
That's correct, but…
I'm no longer young enough
to get tangled up in a mess.
I may look young, but I'm 35.
-Is that relevant?
-Of course it is.
At 35, your skeletal muscle mass
starts decreasing,
and you're too old to get
the youth and job-seeking allowances.
So you have to take good care of yourself.
Well, simply put,
I want to work here
without any issues until I retire.
That's all.
Some of the sweet potatoes
were swapped with imported ones.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
But you did hear it.
I didn't.
I understand what you mean.
I asked too much of the wrong person.
I apologize.
The texture
of the Spicy SweeTato Chips was bad.
And the spicy seasoning
with the sweet potatoes?
It was absolutely the worst.
Right, Mr. Yoon asked
if they could send
the bid market analysis plan tomorrow.
-Tomorrow?
-His place got broken into.
He has to go to the police.
They broke the lock.
The lock?
Yes.
Is it not working?
Is the machine broken?
Why would it be broken?
It worked fine earlier.
What the hell?
What's wrong with this?
Come on.
HUNMIN CONFECTIONERY
It's acting up again.
Come on.
Hey!
Didn't I tell you to get a new one?
Did you?
Many times, in my head.
Get a new one, now.
Um…
HONDURAS KARAOKE
I pushed you away
Only after love has left
Do we realize?
Why did I wander
When you were right beside me?
Now I finally know
The…
Damn it.
I've been thinking.
If you and Ho break up,
I think I'll have to go with him.
Sorry.
You brat.
You'd think Ho gave birth to him.
It's like he's his son.
Yes, he is his son.
Ho raised him since he was two.
Ho and I are done for real.
I have zero intention
of getting back together.
I don't need your pity, so save it.
Don't flatter yourself, Director.
I'm not here as an old classmate.
I'm here as a producer.
I came to persuade you
about the settlement for the last time,
but you're in no state to talk.
Good luck with the lawsuit.
We'll do our best, too.
And this isn't
as your old classmate or a producer
but just as a fellow human being…
Don't say it.
Just get back together with Ho.
I'm never getting back together with him.
I don't want to hate someone anymore.
And I don't want to be hated either.
She's so lazy.
She doesn't even care about the fine dust.
She should clean once in a while.
How can someone be so lazy?
She didn't even put away her laundry.
Damn it.
Come on.
Look.
I…
Hey, my charger.
Since we broke up,
you should've given it back.
Namgung-Jerk, you jerk.
SEO JU-HYEOK
Ju-hyeok, I can't--
Ms. Song?
Mr. Han?
Why do you have Ju-hyeok's phone…
I want to talk to Ju-hyeok one last time.
Please, I'm begging you.
No, I'm the one…
who's begging you.
Don't mistake the genre here.
You're in a soap opera about an affair,
but you're acting like it's pure romance.
It's laughable.
I won't let you get away with this.
I won't let this go.
Just in case,
avoid making a scene
this Thursday and Friday.
I'll be busy then.
I'm hanging up now.
SONG HAE-NA
JAEKANG LAW FIRM
The person you are calling is unavailable.
Please leave a message…
Ju-hyeok, I'm not a child.
Don't worry about me
while you're on your business trip.
Take care of your work.
I'll see you next week.
I love you.
That's not your color.
WHEN THAT DAY COMES
ACTRESS SONG HAE-NA
Ms. Song, where are you?
Are you kidding me?
I just slipped something fun
into Ms. Kang's bag.
Photos of Ju-hyeok and me at the hotel.
How fun, right?
Ms. Song.
Don't do something you'll regret.
I'm curious.
I wonder how well Seo Ju-hyeok's lapdog
can clean up his mess.
DIRECTOR LEE MI-DO
Why so quiet?
I'm thinking.
You know, the photos
are already in the cloud.
You shouldn't get any funny ideas.
Why are you talking down to me?
Isn't talking down essential
for a power trip?
First, explain to me what happened.
I spent over three months
pointing a camera at her.
That's not your color.
Even under a scarf and hat,
I recognized her instantly.
Oh my gosh! I'm so sorry.
It's fine. I'll do it.
-Do you have tissues?
-Okay. Oh my goodness.
I'm sorry.
At first, I thought you were the guy
she was seeing.
Your suit, watch, and shoes
are exactly like his.
But you're much more important.
Just tell me what you want.
First of all, apologize.
About breaking your phone--
No, not that.
Oh.
About investigating your family--
He's not trash, and he's not a jerk.
You can't talk about him like that.
Didn't you break up?
Even so, he doesn't deserve all that.
Wow, it must've been true love.
You still care this much
even after breaking up.
Fine, I apologize.
But…
forget the apology.
Tell me what you really want.
Double my current directing fee.
I want a co-director credit
and a guaranteed 50% stake
in the original work.
Oh, and any articles about my departure
must be agreed upon in advance.
A week should be enough time, right?
HUNMIN CONFECTIONERY R&D CENTER
Hey, Sang-hun.
I'm at the Incheon Research Center
for the Snack Department meeting.
Compare the last consumer survey feedback
with the sensory evaluation results
and send them…
Can we talk for a second, please?
Am I the only one
who thinks we have a thing?
We just had a meal to discuss work.
You're overreacting.
You call that just work?
Yes.
You asked me out on a Friday night
just to ask about grub infestations
in sweet potato fields?
Yes.
Since sweet potatoes
are our main ingredient,
I needed to study them in depth.
And you're in charge of root crops,
so I asked your opinion.
Who asks for an opinion on a Friday night?
I have no personal feelings for you.
Please don't contact me
unless it's for work.
You've got to be kidding me.
Damn it.
Can I have one?
These are strong.
I smoke those, too. Raven Blue.
The person who got me smoking
in high school smoked those.
What a psycho.
Getting a high schooler to smoke these?
Let's head to the meeting.
How does it make sense to swap perilla
for sesame in O-SweeTato Chips?
Whether it makes sense or not
isn't the point right now.
The monsoon wiped out the perilla crops.
We had no choice. Besides,
the Research Team approved
using sesame instead.
The board meeting is in two days.
We can't do a tasting this way.
What does everyone else think?
Do you agree with her?
I can't really tell.
It tastes the same.
-It's fine.
-Yes.
See that, Ms. Park?
Most people can't tell the difference.
Why don't you drop it?
There's definitely an acidic aftertaste.
Since sesame has
a high unsaturated fat content,
it goes rancid faster,
which seems to ruin the aftertaste.
If there's an issue with the ingredients,
I hope we can work things out
through discussion.
If the mix ratio changes,
we'll share the data with Purchasing first
and ask if it's okay.
All right, understood.
We'll do that from now on.
Let's let it slide
for the upcoming board meeting.
We can't make new seasoning now.
I'll make it.
Please, just say it.
About the imported sweet potatoes,
did you report to Manager Yoon
in Snack Team 4?
I didn't.
If you can't trust your direct superior,
you could have reported it to Audit.
Too many people are involved.
Without direct evidence,
like the Distribution Team bribery case,
they'd only punish a few pawns.
Were you trying to drag me
into something so obviously risky?
I'm a bit selfish.
I couldn't do it alone.
Among the people involved,
is there anyone you have a history with?
For example, a secret blood relative?
Or maybe a feud between families?
Are you seeking revenge with this?
Is that your motivation?
Sorry to disappoint,
but there's nothing like that involved.
Are you trying to be
the youngest Assistant Manager,
-then an executive--
-No, I'm not.
So you're doing this for nothing?
That's ridiculous.
It's just my nature.
I can't ignore what I've seen.
Once I'm fixated,
I have to resolve all my doubts.
I can't help but keep digging.
It's not out of
a sense of justice or duty.
I just have a difficult personality.
Okay, I understand.
Since you're so determined,
I'll respect that.
You've heard about Kitchen Lab 3, right?
Oh, you didn't?
You shouldn't be here alone.
It's known to be haunted by a ghost.
It's not just a rumor.
I saw it while working here.
I don't care.
I can beat it.
Wow.
Say hi for me if you see it.
Ask how it's doing.
Yes, I will.
Hey.
CONTEST FOR ENGAGED COUPLES
So,
I heard a wedding hall
was hosting an event for engaged couples,
so I signed you two up.
If you guys enter,
-you'll definitely win first place.
-First place!
Even fifth place gets red ginseng.
You know?
Newlyweds are tired day and night.
Red ginseng is the best choice for energy.
-Red ginseng is the best!
-Right.
Okay, how about fourth place?
A Bellafino coffee machine.
The crema is amazing!
Imagine having a delicious espresso
every morning.
-Yes. Mi-do, you like coffee, right?
-You love it.
Third place gets
a 20-liter Humiel dehumidifier.
It's amazing in the rainy season.
You won't even know it's raining.
So soft and dry.
Second place, Airponic Dress Care.
You always wear dress shirts.
The collars get dirty.
You can't wash them every day.
For first place, a LaRobot robot vacuum.
The top model
with self-navigation and mopping.
Oh?
-What do you think?
-A robot vacuum.
It does it all,
mopping and self-navigation.
-A robot vacuum.
-Mi-do.
You don't even need first place.
Even fifth gets red ginseng.
Now, let's begin
the contest for engaged couples!
Let's start with a big round
of applause and cheers!
BUSINESS COUPLE
Everyone, cheer them on!
-Good luck!
We split it 50-50.
-Don't change your mind later.
-You too.
We have incredible prizes lined up.
TELEPATHY
Now, the first question.
In the morning,
what website does your boyfriend visit
as soon as he wakes up?
Three, two, one.
Please show your answers.
TODAY'S DEALS
Wow!
-That's right! Nice!
-Nice!
-All right!
-You knew it!
What is your girlfriend's
weirdest sleeping habit?
Hold them up.
DOING A FULL 360
All right, awesome!
What is your go-to karaoke song?
-That's it!
-Okay!
A THOUSAND-YEAR LOVE
-Nice!
-They knew it!
SPEED QUIZ
KEYWORD: BICYCLE
I gave you this for our fifth anniversary.
You lost it in a week, and we fought.
Necklace!
That was our third. Think of our fifth.
Oh, when you were in second grade,
this made you break your leg.
-I carried you to school for days.
-Bicycle?
Yes!
Oh! The person you hate most in the world.
Lee Yeong-do!
But another word for him.
-Parasite!
-Not that.
Scumbag, psychopath, total jerk,
a future lonely old man!
Not any of that.
You said you'd rather bite your tongue off
than call him this.
Oppa!
KEYWORD: OPPA
-All right!
-Yes!
TELEPATHY ORIGAMI
Fold it up first,
so the corner touches the top.
-Okay.
Fold both sides to the center,
forming a triangle.
-Okay.
-Next.
Fold the top and both ends back.
-Okay.
Ta-da!
Now, we only have the final game left.
1ST: BUSINESS COUPLE, 520 POINTS
This game is a heart rate test.
It's called "Steal My Heart."
You can turn the tables with this game.
Because the sum of your heart rates
will be your score.
The time limit is one minute.
Let's begin!
-Let's go!
-All right.
I love how the couples
are looking into each other's eyes.
-Hey, they're going up.
-They're going up!
-The numbers don't lie in this game.
-There we go!
-The Heart-stopper Couple's heart rates…
-It's working!
-… are already rising.
-I didn't think it would.
-I thought their feelings had dried up.
-Their hearts are pounding right now!
BUSINESS COUPLE
M 99, F 90
-What?
-What's going on with the Business Couple?
Their numbers suddenly started to drop.
They were way ahead until just now.
They're way too calm right now.
-Welcome.
-Hi.
Grab your promotional item.
You get a free item. Hot Chocolate Chips.
When these first came out,
everyone went crazy.
Now, we give them out as freebies.
You might not believe it,
but we were once like that, too.
Every moment was passionate
and made our hearts flutter.
We only had eyes for each other.
Those were the most sparkling days
of our love.
WHEN THAT DAY COMES
Director Bong Joon-ho's film  Parasite
surpassed ten million viewers
in just 53 days after its release.
The film is demonstrating
its cinematic quality and mass appeal
as it breaks both domestic
and international box office records.
WHEN THAT DAY COMES
MI-DO
It's made another major mark
in Korean film history.
I'll come visit you every weekend.
Actually, no.
I'll come every Friday night after work.
No.
It's a ten-hour round trip.
You'll be too tired.
You've changed.
-Won't you miss me?
-I'm just worried about you getting tired.
No, you've changed.
Whenever I call you and ask you something,
you just go, "Uh-huh."
What do you mean?
Of course I go, "Uh-huh."
What else would I say?
It used to be,
"Mm-hmm," remember?
When did I ever go, "Mm-hmm"?
It was like, "Mm-hmm."
Do it again.
Mm-hmm.
-Again.
-Stop it.
Okay.
Seriously.
Yes, the place is nice.
It's better with four of us in the room.
That's a relief.
I miss you already. What do I do?
Should I send a selfie?
No, selfies aren't the real you.
Hey.
How can I wait until the weekend?
By working hard.
I'll call you later.
Are you allowed to call your girlfriend
while waiting for the potatoes?
I'm sorry.
I've finished the seasoning.
I just need to mix it with the potatoes.
Damn it.
That scared me.
Namgung!
What? No reaction?
Aren't you happy to see me?
What happened? What about your shoot?
It got canceled because of the rain.
I caught a ride with someone
heading to Incheon.
How did you get in?
Ta-da! He ran away when he saw me.
We were short on extras today.
The crew had to fill in.
That's why I'm in this.
What's with this boring reaction?
Should I just leave?
I'm leaving. I really am.
Well?
Wow, that's cold.
You're so dead.
You can't be making
these surprise visits, can you?
No.
Your reaction was so weak.
I never want to do it again.
You're in trouble.
What's with the boring reaction?
Such a buzzkill.
You need to react so I can--
-Wait.
-What do we do?
-Oh, Mr. Eom. You're still here.
-Yes.
Well, I was leaving, then…
How about we leave together?
Let's clock out.
But I haven't finished mixing yet.
What?
Come on, you should've
finished this earlier.
Hold on. What?
Why is the color like this?
What is this?
Did you mix dark chocolate and capsaicin?
Yes, when I tasted them separately,
they were too boring, so I tried this.
Come on, really?
Dark chocolate and capsaicin together?
That can't be… What?
Why is this good?
Sorry?
Why does it work?
Wow, it's interesting.
Here, try it.
It's like
the sweetness embraces the spiciness,
neutralizing and softening it.
Mm.
What… Who is that?
Who? Where?
Over there, right there.
Right by the window.
The spirited lady.
By the window? Where…
Right there! Can't you see her?
The lady in the black skirt
and traditional white top.
There's nobody there.
What do you mean? She's right there!
She's smiling at us, right there!
I'm going to head out first.
-I'll just…
-Um…
Will he be okay?
He's stronger than he looks.
He's the toughest mentally.
-Mi-do, try this.
-What?
What? This is crazy.
-Is it good?
-Yes, it's delicious.
Why is it so good?
What's wrong?
Did you cry today?
What are you talking about?
Come on, what happened?
What do you mean?
The shoot got canceled
because of the rain.
I'm so happy. I was excited to see you.
What happened?
Tell me.
The assistant director…
He always does that.
What? What a crazy bastard.
So?
You should've said it wasn't you.
If you quit now, they'll blame you.
Is that jerk on set?
-I'll get this jerk…
-Then I'll die of embarrassment.
Right, if I cause a scene,
you'll look like a fool.
But staying quiet
makes you look like a fool, too.
Even if you quit,
you should speak up first.
Running away like this isn't like you.
Let's go together.
What do we do?
They say there's no way
we'll get 500 people by tomorrow.
Our shoot overlaps
with  Sonata of the Wind.
The schedule clearly said the 28th.
Wasn't that the old schedule?
-What was that, punk?
-I mean…
-I think so.
-Did you mess up again?
Why are you here?
What will you do?
No one left to blame anymore?
Don't worry.
I'm not here to tattle on you
for blaming me
after you ordered the set to be torn down.
What are you talking about?
Are you crazy?
You know what?
You'll never debut as a director.
I saw your short film.
I finally understood why you act this way.
I see now. An inferiority complex
really eats away at you.
I'll never be like that.
Stealing angles and storyboards
and losing my identity.
Becoming a fossil chasing after
premiere after-parties.
Thank you.
Thanks to you, I'll be a great director.
What is she talking about?
What did you just say?
-What did you say? Let go!
-Sir.
-Please calm down.
-Are you out of your mind?
-Wow, that little…
-Calm down.
It was an honor working with you.
Five hundred people.
Excuse me?
If you can get 500 people by tomorrow,
you're the assistant director
of this production.
So, can you do it?
Okay, ready!
-Action!
-Go!
How did you know?
Since we were young, you've always known
when I've been crying.
Even my mother wouldn't notice.
But you always knew.
Come to think of it…
how did I know?
I could just tell.
When you were sad.
Okay, cut!
Cut!
What are they doing?
What?
Hey! Lee Mi-do!
I said cut!
They're crazy, damn it.
What?
Cut, I said cut!
Cut! She's too excited.
-Look. Hey…
-Sir!
Hey!
Hey, stop… It's all blowing up!
Why are you stopping me?
You should stop them! Everything blew up!
Our movie became the year's biggest hit.
SOLD OUT
Oh Gyeong-su's  When That Day Comes
surpassed ten million viewers today,
becoming the year's top film.
The snack we made
was launched as Hot Chocolate Chips.
HOT CHOCOLATE CHIPS SOLD OUT
It always sold out instantly,
causing an unprecedented shopping frenzy.
It made 30 billion won in three months,
and Hunmin Confectionery's stock
rose 60% to a record high.
HOT CHOCOLATE CHIPS SOLD OUT
And our love was
also hitting an all-time high.
The passion we had back then…
the butterflies…
where did it all go?
When did we lose it all?
Are you crazy?
Did you cry today?
Why were you crying?
What happened this time?
Why do you make me…
worry so much about you?
Lee Mi-do?
Wow, how long has it been?
I almost didn't recognize you.
How have you been?
I've been well. And you?
I've been crazy busy, as usual.
Are you here for my premiere?
THE UNINVITED GUEST
Oh, say hello.
Our studio's CEO…
INFINITE RUSH
NA SEUNG-HO
…and the investment firm employees.
Hello.
This is Director Lee Mi-do.
I'm sure you all know her.
After Spring Comes Winter,
The 13th Season…
-You've mentioned her before.
-Right.
Anyway, Director Lee.
Isn't life so funny?
You used to tell me
that I'd never debut as a director.
But the one who never made
their feature film debut
is you.
Remember what you said to me back then?
I'd like to return the favor now.
Director Lee.
You will never make
your feature film debut.
You've lost your drive
and become stagnant.
The only thing left
is to rot away.
Don't you think?
Enjoy the movie.
It has nothing to do with you now.
Just don't worry about it!
I wish I could do that!
I don't want to care, either.
But I can't help it.
You saw what happened.
We're over.
Mi-do.
Let's try.
If we try--
If I could…
I'd warm us up in the microwave
for just 90 seconds.
I want to go back
to when you were all I needed.
But we can't go back.
Namgung.
Do you want to know our future?
I'll become a burden to you,
and you'll suffocate me.
For three years, five years,
or maybe even ten years,
we'll keep trying for each other.
But Namgung,
in the end,
we'll end up hating each other.
No.
Maybe we already do
and just don't know it.
I don't want that.
I don't want you to hate me.
And I really don't want to hate you.
So I don't want that future.
I don't want to keep going
just to end up miserable.
Why not?
Are you scared?
Does it scare you that much?
More than breaking up with me?
Yes, I'm scared.
Aren't you scared?
I am.
I'm scared, too.
But…
I can't break up with you.
You disappearing from my life
scares me more, Mi-do.
So I…
Mi-do, I…
I want to keep going with you.
No matter how we end up,
even if we're a total mess
at the end of it all,
I still want to take this path.
Let's get married.
Let's get married, Mi-do.
Marry me, Mi-do.
THANK YOU TO CHO HAN-CHEUL, KIM DA-HUIN,
AND OH DONG-MIN
FOR THEIR SPECIAL APPEARANCE
WHEN THAT DAY COMES
MI-DO
Namgung.
I want that spark back with you.
And I hope you feel it with me, too.
His name is Namgung Ho.
He'll be living with us starting today.
Have you talked about that with Hoya?
Hello. My name is Park Su-a.
I look forward to working with you.
You're clingier than I thought, Ms. Park.
Mr. Namgung. This is clear WH.
I've looked into you too.
Apparently, you do everything
Ju-hyeok tells you to.
So I'm a dog?
Hey. Look at you now.
Subtitle translation by Cayle Kim